表面上看来，创建一个项目列表是一件很简单的事情。
On the surface, creating a list of items is simple enough.
Android有一个滚动的视图，你可以放一个linear布局进去
Android includes a Scroll View into which you can place any
依次排列每个元素，构成一个垂直的列表。
linear layout that in turn arranges each item it contains into a vertical list.
注意底部超出屏幕范围的项目
Note the items which have fallen off the bottom off the linear layout. And
此时它们在UI中是不可见的
therefore aren't currently visible in that UI. The Scroll View,
顾名思义，用户可以滚动这个滚动视图来看到下面的内容
as the name suggests, will let the user scroll through the contents of
然而，在内存有限的设备上使用滚动视图是个挑战，
the layout it contains. But there's a challenge associated with that approach on
关键是，在什么时候对用户的交互进行响应
a device with limited memory, and where touch responsiveness is
当你的列表中有50个列表项的话
critically important. If you have 50 items in a list and
而同一时刻屏幕上最多显示10个项目
can fit 10 items on screen at any given time. What's the minimum number of
那么在滑动屏幕的任意一时间点，你需要在内存中维持多少个列表项呢
views you'd need to create in order to scroll through every item on the list?
答案可能不是那么显而易见，想想怎样才能更有效率地
The answer might not be immediately obvious but think about ways in which you
来呈现这个列表
can be more efficient in your use of the views used to display the entire list.